<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Morita Naoki]]></title>
  <link href="http://moritanaoki.org/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://moritanaoki.org/"/>
  <updated>2013-12-01T21:44:22+09:00</updated>
  <id>http://moritanaoki.org/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Morita Naoki]]></name>
    
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[I won the prize of Qiita Hackason]]></title>
    <link href="http://moritanaoki.org/blog/2013/12/01/prize-of-qiita-hackason/"/>
    <updated>2013-12-01T17:56:58+09:00</updated>
    <id>http://moritanaoki.org/blog/2013/12/01/prize-of-qiita-hackason</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I participated in the qiita hackason held at Nov.9.2013 at Daikanyama, Japan. It&rsquo;s theme was to make the iPad App with <strong>Tangiblock</strong> &ndash; The blocks works together with iPad screen, which was invented by the <a href="http://www.benesse.co.jp/english/">Benesse</a> and MIT lab.</p>

<p>It&rsquo;s my first hackason experience! After the presentation of 7 hours development. The developer evaluetes each other. And I won the prize!</p>

<p>At that time, TV clues are there for a whole day for covering the Tngiblock. My presentation was on the TV.</p>

<p><img class="center" src="http://moritanaoki.org/images/blog/201312/qiita_wbs.jpg"></p>

<!-- more -->


<p>The prize was iPad mini Retina Display model. I was very happy because I wanted it, but I already have iPad mini so I gave up to buy this product and will wait for the next version.</p>

<p><img class="center" src="http://moritanaoki.org/images/blog/201312/qiita_prize.jpg" title="" ></p>

<p>During hackason, I was very nervous. But after that, talking with the developers was very fun!</p>

<p>I will participate hackason again!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Octopress Customizing]]></title>
    <link href="http://moritanaoki.org/blog/2013/11/27/octpress-customizing/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-27T04:13:37+09:00</updated>
    <id>http://moritanaoki.org/blog/2013/11/27/octpress-customizing</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>Now I was customizing the Octopress. I&rsquo;m not accustomed to the css and a whole project design &ndash; I think it means I&rsquo;m new to the web site programming, because of that, I just rewrite and add in the theme&rsquo;s base css. I think there are better ways. SCSS???</p>

<p>My choice is <a href="https://github.com/shashankmehta/greyshade">greyshade</a>. I think this choice is not bad, rather good. I can find many blogs using this theme. But almost of all I found out were customized version.</p>

<!--more-->


<p>I want to make a beautiful design blog. Ah, and I tried many themes I found in <a href="https://github.com/imathis/octopress/wiki/3rd-Party-Octopress-Themes">erd Party Octopress Themes</a>. Try, change, and try again. After that, I found that my octopress repository was messed up&hellip;Ah. I deleted many files I thought not important, and copy the original part where I deleted files were.</p>

<p>Ok, it&rsquo;s late at night in Japan. It&rsquo;s a second before morning. I&rsquo;ll have to sleep. Next time, Octopress!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Start blogging again]]></title>
    <link href="http://moritanaoki.org/blog/2013/11/26/start-blogging-again/"/>
    <updated>2013-11-26T23:31:34+09:00</updated>
    <id>http://moritanaoki.org/blog/2013/11/26/start-blogging-again</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>I started writing blog again with Octopress, which is also again. Today, I set up my new Octopress blog. Actually, I wanted to try <a href="https://github.com/shashankmehta/greyshade/tree/master/sass">greyshade/sass at master · shashankmehta/greyshade</a>.</p>

<p>I tried it and made the blog. In today&rsquo;s work, I felt that I have to know a few things.</p>

<ul>
<li>What .sccs is. I wanted to change the looks but I cannot do what I want. Why greyshade.scss are many!!?? Fu~</li>
<li>The jekyl&rsquo;s system. I&rsquo;m very confused the number of greyshade.scss and many base.scss&hellip;</li>
</ul>


<p>Anyway, I felt relieved to be able to make up my new blog.</p>

<!--more-->


<h3>In this blog..</h3>

<p>I want to write about programming things. And I wanted to show Japanese schene!</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
